It stands for Fabrication Laboratory and it comes from MIT.
Here you can 3D printing things-
-You can laser things -kind of a little bit of everything possible.
What is the coolest thing that has been 3d-printed here?
Oops there are a lot of cool stuff-
-But I would say a bust in several different colors.
Do you sometimes feel like a genius?
Just a crazy one.
Why did you choose Halmstad University?
They had a very interesting education-
-And it's a place I've never been to before.
Were you on the zero?
Yes.
How was it?
Among the most fun I've done.
Where are you sitting on campus if you want to look for people?
A little odd question, but trade center, at the top with binoculars.
What do you want to work on after graduation?
I hope.
Tell us something that you think most people do not know about college.
They have a very nice sauna at the sports center.
Now my questions are over.